

const STORE = [
{
  question: 'Where does Spongebob work?',
answers: ['Chum Bucket', 'The Clamshell', 'Krusty Krab', 'The Boating School']},

{question: 'What town does Spongebob live in?',
answers: ['Binky Bottom', 'Bikini Bottom', 'Beach Booty', 'Bubble Butt']},

{question: "What is Spongebob\'s catch phrase?",
answers: ['I\'m ready!', 'Let\'s go!', 'Can\'t catch me!', 'Say who?!']},

{question: 'What is arguably Spongebob\'s favorite activity?',
answers: ['Racing seahorses', 'Building sand castles', 'Popping bubbles', 'Jellyfishing']},

{question: 'Where do Spongebob and Patrick spend ALOT of time?',
answers: ['Goofy Goober\'s Ice Cream Party Boat', 'Gils House of Seaglass and Seagulls', 'Goofy Glob\'s Hot Dog Lounge', 'The Fish Hook Bar & Grill']},

{question: 'What does the first \"U\" in Spongebob\'s F.U.N song stand for?',
answers: ['U is for understanding', 'U is for you and me', 'U is for you are cool','U is for underwater fun']},

{question:'What is Spongebob\'s fishing net called?',
answers: ['Catchin King','Betty Netty','Old Reliable','Jelly McJellin']},

{question:'Flats the Flounder terrorizes Spongebob by threatening to:',
answers: ['Steal his job','Become best friends with Patrick','Eat his pet snail, Gary','Kick his butt']},

{question:'Spongebob has what on his nose when he becomes a lifeguard?',
answers: ['Sunscreen','Glue','Ice cream','Toothpaste']},

{question:'What does Spongebob call the drawing he made with the \"Magic Pencil\"?',
answers: ['Doodle Bob','Jr. Bob','Maggie Man','Cadoodle']}
];

const eachCorrectAnswer = [
  'Krusty Krab',
  'Bikini Bottom',
  'I\'m ready!',
  'Jellyfishing',
  'Goofy Goober\'s Ice Cream Party Boat',
  'U is for you and me',
  'Old Reliable',
  'Kick his butt',
  'Ice cream',
  'Doodle Bob'
  ];